motionworship.com 2017-12-29

# Privacy Policy | Motion Worship – Video Loops, Countdowns, & Moving Backgrounds for the Christian Church

## **MOTION WORSHIP™ LLC WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY**

This policy explains our information practices, defines your privacy options and describes how your information is collected and used. 

This policy covers the website at www.motionworship.com (the “MW Website”). The MW Website is owned and operated by Motion Worship LLC, a limited liability company organized under the laws of Minnesota (“MW”). Should you have privacy questions or concerns, send an email to josiah@motionworship.com or send a letter to us at the following address: Motion Worship LLC, 11116 Xenia Ave N, Champlin, MN 55316.

By visiting and using the MW Website, you agree to the collection and use of information in the manner described in this policy. MW shall have the right at any time and without prior notice, at its sole discretion, to revise this policy. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you at this MW Website, by email, by means of a notice the next time you log in to the MW Website, or by means of a notice on the MW Website homepage. Such revisions and additions shall be effective immediately upon notice. You are responsible for reviewing the MW Website periodically for any modification to this policy. Any access or use of the MW Website by you after notice of modifications to this policy shall constitute and be deemed to be your agreement to such modifications.

## **The Information we Collect**

This policy applies to all information collected on the MW Website and any information you provide to MW. You will most likely provide personal information to us when you register as a user of MW Website, purchase the services offered by MW or participate in certain MW promotions or events. The personal information we may collect includes: your name, passwords, usernames, addresses, email addresses, phone numbers, debit card information, credit card information and PayPal account information.

## **Blogs and Product Ratings**

The MW Website may include blogs, product ratings or other message areas that allow users to post or send information to the MW Website. When you post information to the MW Website, other site visitors can also view that information. We urge you to exercise caution when providing personally identifiable information to MW or the MW Website. 

## **Our Collection of Your Data**

In addition to the personal information you supply, we may collect certain information to evaluate how visitors, guests, and customers use the MW Website. We collect data to make the MW Website work better for you in the following ways: to improve the design of the MW Website, to provide personalization on the MW Website and to evaluate the performance of our marketing programs. The technologies we may use to gather this non-personal information may include “IP” addresses, “cookies”, browser detection, and “weblogs”. 

## **How we Use Information**

Our primary goal in collecting your information is to provide you with a personalized, relevant, and positive experience with the MW Website. 

You can register on the MW Website to receive promotions and updates, or to be contacted for market research purposes. You can control your privacy preferences regarding such marketing communications (see the section below entitled “Your Privacy Preferences”).

From time to time, you may be invited to participate in optional customer surveys or promotions, and MW may request that you provide some or all of the above listed personal information in those surveys or promotions. We use information collected from surveys and promotions to learn about our customers in order to improve our services and develop new products and services of interest to our customers.

IP addresses define the Internet location of computers and help us better understand the geographic distribution of our visitors and customers and manage the performance of the MW Website. Cookies are tiny files placed onto the hard drive of your computer when you visit the MW Website, so we can immediately recognize you when you return to the MW Website and deliver content specific to your interests. You may modify your browser preferences to accept all cookies, be notified when a cookie is set, or reject all cookies. Please consult your browser instructions for information on how to modify your choices about cookies. If you modify your browser preferences, certain features of the MW Website may not be available to you.

We may detect the type of web browser you are using to optimize the performance of the MW Website and to understand the mix of browsers used by our visitors, guests, and customers. To learn about how people use our site, we examine weblogs, which show the paths people take through the MW Website and how long they spend in certain areas.

MW may contract with unaffiliated third parties to provide services such as customer communications, website analytics and other services. When we do this, we may provide your personally identifiable information to third parties only to provide those services, and they are not authorized to use your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

## **Our Commitment to Data Security**

Access to your data is limited to authorized MW staff or approved vendors (such as payment systems). MW will not sell, rent, lease or exchange your personal information with other organizations, except as set forth herein. All credit card data is stored securely at Authorize.net and/or PayPal.com. All sensitive personal information is gathered and accessed using SSL encryption. Although total security does not exist on the Internet, MW shall make commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard the information that you submit to MW or that MW collects.

## **Use of the MW Website by Children**

The MW Website is not intended for use by children under the age of 13. 

## **Your Privacy Preferences**

When you sign up as a registered user of the MW Website you may begin receiving marketing communications such as e-mail newsletters, product and service updates and promotions. Our customers generally find this type of information useful. If you do not want to receive these updates, you can opt-out by using any of the following methods: select the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the email and follow the opt-out instructions; or send an email to josiah@motionworship.com. 

## **How to Access or Correct Your Information**

You can access and maintain your personally identifiable information that we collect by visiting the account link in the main menu of the MW Website or by sending an email to josiah@motionworship.com. To protect your privacy and security, we require a user ID and password to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to such personally identifiable information.

## **Disclosure of Information**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process. It is also possible that MW would sell the company or all or substantially all of its assets. In any transaction of this kind, customer information, including your personally identifiable information, may be among the assets that are transferred. If we decide to so transfer your personally identifiable information, you will be notified by an email sent to the last known email address in our files and/or by notice posted on the MW Website.

## **Privacy and Other Websites**

The MW Website may contain links to other websites. MW is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site, and to read the privacy statements of each website that collects personally identifiable information. Some linked sites may be co-branded with our trademarks and those of our business partners. They may have the look and feel of the MW Website, but the URL in your browser window will indicate that you are visiting a different site. This policy only applies to information collected by MW.

Last Updated: February 21st, 2013
